(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-18T00:00:47.753245",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Grimoire 4 Ever
〜四人で綴られ、永遠に残る魔導書〜
~A Grimoire Written by Four, Lasting Forever~
＃ねぽらぼ6周年3Dライブ
#Nepolabo 6th Anniversary 3D Live
Grimoire 4 Ever ～四人で綴られ、永遠に残る魔導書～
Grimoire 4 Ever ~Written by four, a grimoire that remains forever~
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
獅白ぼたん
Shishiro Botan
Grimoire 4 Ever ～四人で綴られ、永遠に残る魔導書～
Grimoire 4 Ever ~Written by four, a grimoire that remains forever~
Twinkle 4 You (Grimoire Remix)
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reach you, melody of the stars
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Pack my feelings tight, so tight
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
This harmony I play with you
これからもずっと続いていく
Will continue forever from now on
ねえねえ もっと近くにおいでよ
Hey, hey, come a little closer
回り始めた世界で踊らない？終わらない
Won't you dance in this spinning world? It won't end
わくわく 魔法かけたら
When we cast a thrilling spell
ドキドキは sync して ほら party time 止まらない
Look, our heartbeats sync, party time won't stop
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
With a wish inside
Twinkle Twinkle
夜空で歌いましょう
Let's sing in the night sky
君に響け 星のメロディー
Echo to you, melody of the stars
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing a new constellation
君と繋がっているこの宇宙に
In this sky where I'm connected with you
宝石をちりばめよう
Let's scatter jewels
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reach you, melody of the stars
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Pack my feelings tight, so tight
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
This harmony I play with you
これからもずっと続いていく
Will continue forever from now on
Clap Clap ほら一緒に鳴らそう
Clap, clap, look, let's make some noise together
この瞬間をキャッチして忘れない Stary Night
Catch this moment, an unforgettable starry night
キラキラ魔法解けても
Even if the sparkling magic fades
胸にしまったトキメキは消えない止まらない
The excitement locked in my heart won't vanish, won't stop
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
With a wish inside
Twinkle Twinkle
夜空で踊りましょう
Let's dance in the night sky
Twinkle 4 you
君と残す 星のメモリー
The starry memory I leave with you
想い出ギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Pack our memories tight, so tight
…ね。君と会えたこの素敵な奇跡と夢を
...with you. This wonderful miracle and dream we shared...
また叶えよう
Let's make them come true once again.
君に響け 星のメロディ
Echoing to you, the melody of the stars.
新しい星座を描いて
Let's draw a brand new constellation.
君と繋がっているこの宇宙(そら)に
In this sky where I'm connected to you...
星屑を 散りばめよう
...let's sprinkle stardust all around.
君に届け 星のメロディ
Reach out to you, the melody of the stars.
想いをギュッと ギュッと詰め込んで
Squeezing all our feelings tight inside...
君と奏でるこのハーモニー保存
...and this harmony I play with you...
これからもずっと 続いていく
...will continue on forever and ever.
La La La...
イェーイ！
Yeah!
お集まりいただきありがとうございます！
Thank you all for gathering here today!
というわけで皆さん、ねぽらぼ6周年記念3Dライブ『Grimoire Forever』にお越しいただきありがとうございます！
And so, everyone, thank you so much for coming to Nepolabo's 6th Anniversary 3D Live, "Grimoire Forever"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はーい、我らー…
Alright, we are...
ねぽらぼでーす！
Nepolabo!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
というわけで、簡単な自己紹介、ねねからどうぞ！
Now then, let's do quick introductions. Nene, go ahead!
はい！ホロライブ5期生、オレンジの魔法、ピンクの桃尻…
Yes! Hololive's 5th generation, orange magic, pink peach-butt...
みんなのエナジードリンク、桃鈴ねねでーす！
...everyone's energy drink, Momosuzu Nene!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you very much!
はい、ポルカです！ポルカ、おるか？おるよー！
Yes, it's Polka! Is Polka here? I'm here!
赤色の魔法で合ってるのかな？
I guess I'm the red magic, right?
はい、ポルカです。よろしくお願いします！
Yes, it's Polka. Nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
次はラミィ！
Next is Lamy!
はい！ホロライブの過保護が肝臓、雪花ラミィです！
Yes! Hololive's overprotected liver, Yukihana Lamy!
青色の魔法でーす。よろしくお願いします！
I'm the blue magic. Nice to meet you!
おー、肝臓…
Oh, liver...
はい、じゃあねぽらぼの『ぼ』！
Alright, now the "Bo" of Nepolabo!
黒魔道士、獅白ぼたんです！よろしくお願いします！
The black mage, Shishiro Botan! Nice to meet you!
黒魔道士！かっこいい！
Black mage! So cool!
この世のすべてを滅ぼす…
To destroy everything in this world...
はい！今回の配信のハッシュタグはこちら！
Yes! Here is the hashtag for today's stream!
ハッシュタグ『ねぽらぼ6周年3Dライブ』！こちらでお願いします！
Hashtag "Nepolabo 6th Anniversary 3D Live"! Please use this!
おねがいしまーす！
Please do!
皆さん、たくさんポストしてくださいね！ラミィたちもチェックします！
Everyone, please post a lot! We'll be checking them too!
トレンド1位を目指しましょう！
Let's aim for the number one trending spot!
そして、いよいよ周年ライブ始まりましたけど、どうですか皆さん、わくわくどきどき？
And now, the anniversary live has finally started, but how is everyone feeling? Excited and nervous?
わくわくどきどき！どきどきわくわく！
Excited and nervous! Nervous and excited!
そんなねね、今回のライブコンセプトを説明していただけますか？
So Nene, could you explain the concept of today's live?
コンセプトはね、『8月の魔法』！
The concept is "August Magic"!
キャッチコピーは、『4人で綴られ、永遠に残る魔導書』
The tagline is "A grimoire written by four, remaining forever".
魔法少女をイメージとした、帽子とステッキを特別に作っていただきました！
We had custom hats and wands made, inspired by magical girls!
おー！
Oh!
そうですね、そのコンセプトに合うステージも作っていただきました！
That's right, we also had a stage built that fits the concept perfectly!
すごい！壮大！
Amazing! So grand!
これ、うちら浮いてる？宇宙に
Are we floating? In space?
ねー、浮いてる！星空に囲まれたステージで、今日はライブをするんだね！
Yeah, floating! We're performing on a stage surrounded by the starry sky today!
そういうことです！
That's exactly right!
すごい！
Incredible!
あ、見てこれ！専用の魔法陣！
Ah, look at this! Our own magical circles!
すごーい！
So cool!
ねねさん、ねねさん、あっち、あっち！
Nene, Nene, over there, over there!
え、どこ？あ、ここ？
Huh, where? Ah, here?
これ、専用魔法陣もあるから、ライブでいっぱい見せていきたいね！
We have our own magic circles, so we want to show them off a lot during the live!
そんな中でね、1曲目からみんなでちょっと魔法とかも、こう掛けまくっちゃったわけですけれども
With all that, we were casting spells right from our very first song.
どうでしたか？魔法
How was the magic?
魔法掛けてた！えーと、まず1曲目の『twinkle 4 you』を、『Grimoire Remix』ということで
We were casting magic! First, our first song, "twinkle 4 you", was the "Grimoire Remix".
新しくリミックスしていただきました！ちょっと違ったでしょ、いつもと
We had it newly remixed! It was a bit different from usual, right?
違ったよね！いつもと
It really was! From usual.
ちょっとタイミング難しいとことかあるんだよね
There are some parts where the timing is a bit tricky.
そうそう！そこ難しかったけど、なんとか今日も頑張りましたね、皆さん！
Yes, yes! It was difficult, but we all managed to pull it off today!
頑張りました！
We did our best!
で、そして魔導書に魔法で映像投影したり、あと歌詞もさ、この上の方に出したりしてもらいました
And then, we projected images onto the grimoire with magic, and had the lyrics displayed up above.
ね、この空間に
Yeah, in this space.
魔法に頑張っていただきました！
We had the magic work hard for us!
うちらも魔法とかやってたけど、今、できるんですか？
We were casting magic too, but can we do it right now?
あ、できるの？
Oh, we can?
見逃した人もいるかもしれないので、ポルカたち実はもう、今回の今日のためにこうやって魔法のステッキも用意してもらったってことで、魔法が使えるんですわ！
Since some of you might have missed it, we actually had these magical wands prepared for today, so we can use magic!
おー、使えるんだ！
Oh, we can use it!
じゃ、ポルカね、やってみようかな。
Well, Polka will try next.
おお、いいよいいよ、やってやって
Oh, sure, sure, do it, do it!
じゃあ、ハートを出します。
Now, I'll bring out a heart.
うーん、そい、そい、そい、そい、そい。はっ！
Hmm, soi soi soi soi soi. Ha!
そういう感じなんだ
So that's how it is.
あ、なんか可愛い。ハート出たね。
Ah, it's cute. A heart came out, right?
これ、うちらも出せるの？
Can we also bring them out?
え、やってみる？
Want to try?
あ、じゃあ、ししろ行ってみる？
Oh, then, shall Shishiro go?
ししろ、ふん、はっ！
Shishiro, hmm, ha!
出し方、出し方そんな感じなんだ
The way she brought it out...
可愛い、可愛いけど、可愛いけど...
Cute, cute but, cute but...
ラミィもやってよ。/ あ、いいよ。
Lamy, you do it too! / Ah, okay.
はいっ！
Yes!
ラブ注入♡
Love Injection!
うわ、飛んだ！うわー、すごい！
Wow, it flew! Wow, amazing!
ねねちも、ねねちも。
Nenechi too, Nenechi too!
ええー...
Eeh...
ラブ注入、う、ももじり！
Love Injection... Peach butt!
ちょっと待って。
Wait a minute.
魔法が分かんなくなってきた、これじゃあ。
I can't tell what magic this is anymore.
面白いなぁ。
This is fun.
でも、せっかくだからね、みんなの魔法をもっと見せてほしいなと思うんですけど...
But, since we're here, I want to see more of everyone's magic...
おっ？
Oh?
ねねち、何ですか？
Nenechi, what is it?
まずは手始めにね、ねねが。
First, as a start, Nene will...
この空間をちょっとだけ、変えたいと思います！
I'll change this space just a little bit!
みんな何が変わるかよく見ててね。
Everyone, watch carefully to see what changes.
え、変わるの？分かんない、分かんないことある？
Eh, it will change? I don't know, is there something we won't notice?
うーーーー、えいっ！
Uhhhhh... Ei!
え？何？おおおお！
Eh? What? Ohhhh!
でっかい！でっかい！迫ってきてる、迫ってきてる！
It's huge! Huge! It's coming closer, coming closer!
迫ってきた、迫ってきた、びっくりした。
It came closer, came closer, I was surprised.
すごーい、大きい。魔導書が大きくなった！
Amazing, so big. The magic book got bigger!
いいじゃん。
Nice!
えー、大迫力！
Wow, so impactful!
じゃあ、この魔導書をちょっと使ってさ、
Then, let's use this magic book to...
お、私たちの召喚魔法を見せようじゃないですか。
Oh, show them our summoning magic.
えっ！ししろそんなものが使えるのか？
What! Shishiro, you can use that?
これはね、みんなのパワーが要ります。
For this, I need everyone's power.
なるほど、頑張ろう。
I see, let's do our best.
じゃあ、ちょっと行きますよ、お祈りしてね。/ はーい。
Well, here I go. Pray for it. / Okay!
じゃあ、行きますよ。せーの！
Then, here we go. Ready, set...
うーーーーーーーーーー！
Uhhhhhh!
おおおお！出た！かっこいい！
Ohhhh! It's here! Cool!
何が来る、何が来る？
What's coming, what's coming?
うわあああ！来た！
Waaah! They came!
降りてきてる！ありがとう！
They're coming down! Thank you!
ネコ！ゆきみ！
Nekko! Yukimi!
SSRB！だいくちゃん！
SSRB! Daiku-chan!
召喚できました！
We successfully summoned them!
よかった、召喚成功！やったね。
Great, summoning successful! We did it!
じゃあ、一緒にね、これでみんなも集合したことだし、ね、見守っていてくれるか？
Well, together, now that everyone has gathered, will you keep watch over us?
ありがとう、見守っててね、ありがとう！
Thank you, watch over us, thank you!
よし、じゃあそろそろ次の曲いっちゃいましょうか！ / はーい。
Alright, then shall we move on to the next song? / Yes!
待って、さっきので結構MP使ったけど大丈夫そう？マジックポイント。
Wait, we used quite a lot of MP earlier, are you okay? Magic points.
まだまだ、まだまだ行けますよ！全然いけるよ、いけそう？
Not yet, we can still go! Definitely, can we do it?
オッケー、じゃあこの後も楽しんでいってください！
Okay, then please keep enjoying after this!
それでは、つ、つ、次の曲、レッツゴー！ / いぇーい。
Now then, to the n-n-next song, let's go! / Yay!
楽しんでね！
Enjoy!
悪戯に君をずっと見ていた訳じゃない 僕の考えを当ててごらんよ
I wasn't just looking at you playfully, try to guess what I'm thinking.
些細な仕草 視線 瞬き 君はもう掌に
A slight gesture, a glance, a blink, you are already in the palm of my hand.
剥き出しのtrapなんてかかる訳ないわ
There's no way I'd fall for such an obvious trap.
甘い言葉にも惑わされない
And I won't be swayed by sweet words either.
心の奥の奥の奥まで見透かしちゃうよ
I can see right through to the very depths of your heart.
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, why you know?
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, why do you know?
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, I know it.
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, understand?
Meaning, meaning of love. \"Are you ready?\"
自覚ないでしょうね思い通りに
You probably don't even realize
君は動かされている事！
that you're being moved exactly as I planned!
単純じゃないの駆け引きのhintを
It's not that simple, don't miss
全て見落とさないで
any of the hints in this game of love.
Meaning of love, meaning of love, 加速していく
Meaning of love, meaning of love, accelerating.
Meaning of love, meaning of love, 二人の鼓動
Meaning of love, meaning of love, our two heartbeats.
Meaning of love, meaning of love, 心理戦は
Meaning of love, meaning of love, this psychological battle...
次のstageへ
...is moving to the next stage.
虚ろなその目に私はどう映るの
How do I reflect in those hollow eyes of yours?
とても煌びやかでまるでcinderella
So dazzling, just like Cinderella.
突き刺さる視線ズキンと感じて 君に余裕見せつけて
Feeling your piercing gaze throb, I'll show you my composure.
あからさま過ぎてお腹が捩れるよ
It's so obvious, it's making me double over with laughter.
既に君はもう出来上がってる
You're already completely under my spell.
頭で次の次の次の日まで見通さなくちゃ
I have to foresee in my head up to the next, next, next day.
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, why you know?
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, why do you know?
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, I know it.
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, understand?
It's a joking feeling...
Understand?
Meaning of life... Are you ready?
唯一無二のジョーカーを手にするために
To make the one and only Joker mine,
欲望さらけ出しているポート
exposing all my desires at port.
離れてく世界のロジックを
Can you enjoy the logic
君は楽しめるかい？
of a drifting world?
重要なキーは
The crucial key is...
全てシークレット
all a secret.
後戻りはできないステージへ
To a stage where there's no turning back.
揺らいでるでしょう ここにいる意味さえも
You must be wavering, even about the meaning of being here.
切札はそれぞれ 互いの手札に
Each of us holds a trump card in our hands.
頭と心で暴き出して
Expose it with your mind and heart,
胸を撃ち抜いて
and shoot right through the chest!
自覚ないでしょうね 思い通りに
You probably don't realize it, but just as expected,
君は動かされていること
you're being controlled.
単純じゃないの 駆け引きのヒントを
It's not simple. Gather every single hint
全て拾って
of this bargaining.
唯一無二のジョーカーを手にすることで
By getting our hands on the one and only Joker,
理解できた愛のカタチを
we finally understood the shape of love.
誰かに仕組まれていても
Even if it was set up by someone,
最後に笑う君と
I'll be with you who laughs in the end.
加速してく
Our heartbeats...
二人の鼓動
are accelerating.
心理戦は次のステージへ
Our psychological war moves onto the next stage.
Oh oh oh... Oh yeah
La la la...
ござる ござる
Gozaru, gozaru,
何でもござると
anything goes-de gozaru!
切り捨て御免のマジカルワールド
No excuse for cutting you down in this magical world!
I-N-D! I-N-D!
魔法の呪文 I-N-D!
The magical spell is I-N-D!
ましかるござる Let's go!
Mashikaru Gozaru, Let's go!
朝 目が覚めたら 遅刻寸前
When I woke up in the morning, I was on the verge of being late!
お気に入りのわらじを履いたなら
Once I put on my favorite straw sandals,
駆け抜けいる アスファルト
I run across the asphalt!
忍（もっと）！刀（チャキン）！チャキン！これがマジカルワンド
More! Clank! Clank! This is my magical wand!
どこから見ても 魔法（しょぼ）ナリ
No matter how you look at it, it's magical (shabby)!
ひれ伏せ 者共！
Bow down, everyone!
一歩 動こう奴
Those who take a step,
悪代官 奴らたち
evil magistrates and their lackeys!
ちょっと 弱い？
A bit weak?
だいぶ 可愛い？
Very cute?
拙者のワンドのお供になるでござる！
You shall become the companion of my wand-de gozaru!
マジカルワンド斬り！
Magical Wand Slash!
ござる ござる
Gozaru, gozaru,
討ち入りでござる
it's a raid-de gozaru!
マジカルな峰打ちをお見舞いするでござる
I'll treat you to a magical strike with the back of my blade-de gozaru!
ござるプリンセス
Gozaru Princess!
ござる ござる
Gozaru, gozaru,
この世界を守る
protecting this world!
完璧に可憐な 姿ご覧あれ
Behold my perfectly lovely form!
魔法少女 ましかるござる
Magical girl, Mashikaru Gozaru!
フリフリヒラヒラ そよ風に舞う
Furi furi hira hira, dancing in the gentle breeze,
袴の裾を ちょいとつまんで決めポーズ
holding the hem of my hakama slightly to strike a pose,
崇めよ 者共！
worship me, everyone!
ござらんなんのの
How about that?
麗しきお姫様
A beautiful princess...
解けない
whose true identity...
その正体
cannot be solved.
秘密こそ史上最大のトレンドでござる
Secrets are the biggest trend in history-de gozaru!
ござる ござる
Gozaru, gozaru,
闇打ちでござる
it's a sneak attack-de gozaru!
魔法少女は座らねど 高い用事でござる
Magical girls don't sit, but they have high affairs-de gozaru!
ござるプリンセス
Gozaru Princess!
ござる ござる
Gozaru, gozaru,
魔法の国から
from the magical kingdom,
お忍びで舞い降りた 謎の転校生
an undercover mysterious transfer student who flew down!
魔法少女 ましかるござる
Magical girl, Mashikaru Gozaru!
そんな風に素敵を 作りたい
I want to make wonderful things like that...
魔法少女ましかる☆ござる
[Song: Magical Girl Mashikaru Gozaru]
ねえ、可愛くありたいと願う
Hey, I wish to stay cute
忘れちゃいけない魔法 守りたいでござる
I want to protect the magic we mustn't forget, gozaru!
ござる ござれ いつまでもござる
Gozaru, gozare, always gozaru!
胸キュンな一撃をお見舞いするでござる
I'll deliver a heart-throbbing blow, gozaru!
ござる ござれ この世界を守る
Gozaru, gozare, protecting this world!
完璧に可憐な姿
Feast your eyes...
ご覧あれ
...on my perfectly lovely form!
魔法少女まじかるござる
Magical Girl Magical Gozaru!
I-M-C I-M-C 魔法の呪文
I-M-C I-M-C, the magic spell!
I-M-C まじかるござる レッツゴー！
I-M-C, Magical Gozaru, let's go!
ビビデバ
[Song: Bibideba]
つまらないデイズもう散々ね！
I'm totally done with these boring days!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
Living a life of just wishing for miracles!
watch me do - do - do - do - do
Watch me do-do-do-do-do!
呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
Secret spells, magic with no tricks!
I wanna be free！だってまだふりだし
I wanna be free! Because I'm back at the start!
hey タクシー ちょっと宇宙迄
Hey taxi, take me to outer space!
秒針は音を立てて
The second hand makes a sound...
夜を急かす魔物のように
...like a monster urging the night on.
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Life is magic that melts away in an instant.
それならば駆け抜け思い通り
If so, I'll run through it just as I please!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って drivin'
Jumping onto a stylish carriage, drivin'!
あたしは大返身メイクアップ
I'm undergoing a major makeover!
我儘のまにまに 燦きに注意
Indulging my selfishness, watch out for the sparkle!
洒落た街で dancin'
Dancin' in a stylish city!
様々ならグッバイ劣等感
Say goodbye to inferiority complex!
何時かは喝采クラップオウデエエンス
One day, applause from the audience!
皆皆御唱和あれ
Everyone, sing along with me!
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boo - wa)
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boowa, yeah)
混絡がっても仕様が無い
It can't be helped if it gets tangled,
ガラスシューズで踊る tonight
dancing in glass shoes tonight!
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boo - wa)
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boowa, yeah)
今夜に明日など無い
There is no tomorrow to tonight.
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
So the one who dances freely wins, right?
da - da - da - da - dance ラリラリホ
Da-da-da-da-dance, rari-rari-ho!
どんな問題も解は一つ
No matter the problem, there's only one solution.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す
Loving the blank pages, correct answers, and mistakes...
本当のあたしの理想
That's my true ideal.
なんだか世界は限界の気配がして
Somehow, the world feels like it's reaching its limit,
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
just staying safe only makes me worry.
今すぐ jumpin', jumpin' out
Right now, jumpin', jumpin' out!
chitty - chitty, bang - bang
chitty, bang - bang
唯々諾々に危機感抱く日々に
In days of harboring a sense of crisis in blind obedience,
ぎりぎり爆発気味
on the verge of exploding,
たった今発散してしまおうか
should I just let it all out right now?
まだまだビイビイ弾巧みに乱射
Still skillfully rapid-firing BBs,
一発じゃあ撃ち足りないわ
one shot is just not enough!
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
The answer I've finally drawn for you,
灰に成る迄踊って居よう
let's dance until we turn to ash!
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boo - wa)
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って drivin'
Jumping onto a stylish carriage, drivin'!
あたしは大返身メイクアップ
I'm undergoing a major makeover!
我儘のまにまに 燦きに注意
Indulging my selfishness, watch out for the sparkle!
洒落た街で dancin'
Dancin' in a stylish city!
様々ならグッバイ劣等感
Say goodbye to inferiority complex!
何時かは喝采クラップオウデエエンス
One day, applause from the audience!
皆皆御唱和あれ
Everyone, sing along with me!
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boo - wa)
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boowa, yeah)
混絡がっても仕様が無い
It can't be helped if it gets tangled,
ガラスシューズで踊る tonight
dancing in glass shoes tonight!
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boo - wa)
(bibbidi - bobbidi - boowa, yeah)
今夜に明日など無い
There is no tomorrow to tonight.
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
So the one who dances freely wins, right?
(今夜に明日など無い)
(There is no tomorrow to tonight)
(ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？)
(So the one who dances freely wins, right?)
召喚ショーケース ～異世界転移した先でフェネックが悪魔の象徴!?冒険から追放されたので、歌とダンスで世界を変えます！～
[Summon Showcase: Reincarnated in another world, a fennec fox is the symbol of evil!? Exiled from the adventure, I'll change the world with song and dance!]
GAME OVER
ハッ！ここはどこ？私はポルカ
Ah! Where am I? I'm Polka!
車にはねられて...
I was hit by a car...
気がついたら知らない人たちに囲まれている
And when I realized, I was surrounded by strangers!
これっていわゆる異世界転移！？
Is this... a reincarnation in another world!?
なんでこっちに剣を向けてるんですか！？
Why are you pointing swords at me!?
何がなんだか大ピンチ！
I don't know what's going on, but I'm in big trouble!
とりあえず逃げっ...
Anyway, let's run...!
よっしゃいくぞー！
Alright, let's go!
冒険の刑 No Way
Sentence of adventure... No Way!
どうすれば
What should we do?
歌って踊ればきっと大丈夫
If we sing and dance, I'm sure it'll be alright!
さあ、ツメの鋭いキミも
Come on, you with the sharp claws,
キバのすごいキミも
and you with the amazing fangs,
Raise your hands!
アガっちゃえ
Let's turn it up!
召喚ショーケース
Summon Showcase!
Oh yeah!
カワイイは力最強は
Cuteness is power! The strongest is...
この世界でも共通の
the love and peace...
ラブ＆ピース
common even in this world!
剣と魔法じゃ作れない未来
A future that can't be made with swords and magic,
今、作れそうな気がした
now, I feel like we can create it.
怖い顔してないで はい、ニコッ
Don't look so scary! Now, smile!
1、2、3...
One, two, three...
召喚ショーケース！
Summon Showcase!
魔王と仲良くなった尾丸ポルカは 平和条約を結ぶことに成功しました
Omaru Polka, who befriended the Demon King, successfully signed a peace treaty.
剣も魔法も使うことはありませんでしたが
Neither swords nor magic were ever used, but...
世界に平和をもたらした彼女は 勇者だったのかもしれません
...she who brought peace to the world might have been a hero.
ハッピーギラファ〜〜！！
Happy Giraffa!!
ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！
Welcome to Nenechi's Giragira Fan Meeting!
さぁ！ツノと顎をながーーく伸ばして
Now, stretch your horns and jaws real long,
思いっきり、楽しんじゃおうね！
and let's have the absolute best time!
それじゃあ、いっくよ〜〜！
All right, here we go!
アミーゴ！カケーロ！ビバ！ギラファ！
Amigo! Kakero! Viva! Giraffa!
kabu-kuwa ギラギラ最高だね kabu-kuwa
Beetle-stag! Shimmering is the absolute best, beetle-stag!
Amore kabu-kuwa yeah!
Amore beetle-stag, yeah!
kabu-kuwa クリクリおめめラブ kabu-kuwa
Beetle-stag! Loving those big round eyes, beetle-stag!
Asore kabu-kuwa yeah!
Here we go, beetle-stag, yeah!
愛のダンスはムーチョムーチョ
The dance of love is mucho mucho!
飛んでシュビドゥバメロメロ
Fly high, shoo-be-doo-bah, totally smitten!
みんな集まれゾロゾロ
Everyone gather round in crowds!
こんChu☆ Chu☆
Kon-kiss, kiss!
パヤパヤパヤパパ
Paya-paya paya-pa!
すごーい！みんなのおかげで、
Amazing! Thanks to everyone...
こんなにたくさんのカブクワたちが集まってくれたよー！
...so many beetles and stags have gathered here!
自分に拍手ー！そして、
Give yourselves a hand! And then...
自然に拍手ーー！
...applaud naturally!
ギラファ ギラファ ギラファ ギラファ
Giraffa, Giraffa, Giraffa, Giraffa!
強くてカッコ良い
Strong and so cool!
ギラギラファンタスティックなノコギリは
These shimmering, fantastic jaws...
宝物だよ
...are treasures!
アミーゴ！カケーロ！ビバ！ギラファ！
Amigo! Kakero! Viva! Giraffa!
kabu-kuwa
Beetle-stag!
こんChu☆
Kon-kiss,
Chu☆
kiss!
パヤパヤ
Paya-paya,
パヤパパ
paya-pa!
っと！じゃあ、これから一緒に
Oops! Well then, from now on, together...
スペシャルなトレーニング、やっちゃおっかな〜〜？？
...shall we do some special training?
足を肩幅に開いて、手を前にして...
Spread your feet shoulder-width, extend your hands forward...
芝刈りパンプアップ、はっじめるよー！
Let's begin the Lawnmower Pump Up!
ブーン！バリバリバリバリ...
Vroom! Pump-pump-pump-pump...
ムキムキな Love me
Muscular, love me!
バキバキで Burning
Ripped and burning!
そう 燃えるカラダ
Yes, this burning body!
ほらね 誰も彼も 振り返るでしょ
See, absolutely everyone is turning to look!
ねぇ 見せつけてやろ
Hey, let's show it off!
腰には ヴィーナスえくぼ
Venus dimples on our lower back!
やれんのか Muscle
Can you do it, muscle?
止まらない Work Out
An unstoppable workout!
最強に、なりたいかァーッ！？
Do you want to become the strongest?!
Yeahーーッ！ムキムキになりたいかァーッ！？
Yeah! Do you want to get muscular?!
Yeahーーッ！この世の全てを守り抜く、祝福が欲しいかァーーッ！？
Yeah! Do you want the blessing that protects all in this world?!
Yeahーーッ！やるしかないっしょ バリバリで Work Out!
Yeah! We've got no choice but to work out intensely!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle, no life! No muscle, no life!
脳筋べっぴんな ヴィーナス
A muscle-brained beautiful Venus!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle, no life! No muscle, no life!
お端さんも マッチョ マッチョ
Even your neighbor is macho macho!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle, no life! No muscle, no life!
やる気ホンキ 大好き
True motivation, I love it!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle, no life! No muscle, no life!
頑張るキミと マッチョ マッチョ
Macho macho with you who does your best!
Yeah!
がおってこ！がおってこ！ がおってこ！がおってこ！
Roar away! Roar away! Roar away! Roar away!
きみのがおが聞こえると そんな日もちょっとやさしくなる
When I hear your roar, even those tough days become a bit gentler.
おすそわけしたくて 踊って踊って踊ってんだ
Wanting to share this with you, I keep dancing on and on.
がおってこ！がおってこ！ ジャンプするなら今しかないし
Roar away! Roar away! If you're going to jump, now is the only time!
がおってこ！がおってこ！ 高いトコ目指しちゃおうよ Let's go!
Roar away! Roar away! Let's aim high, Let's go!
がおってこ！がおってこ！ 小声でも Say ちゃんと聴こえてる
Roar away! Roar away! Even if it's a whisper, say it, I can hear you.
がおってこ！がおってこ！ じゃあ叫んだら未来に届く！？
Roar away! Roar away! Then if we shout, will it reach the future?!
がおってこ！がおってこ！ みんなでなら 446デシベル
Roar away! Roar away! If we're all together, 446 decibels!
がおってこ！がおってこ！ ここがそう 私たちの最高
Roar away! Roar away! This is indeed our absolute best!
Rawr rawr!! Yeah!
言葉にすると真っ直ぐすぎて
Putting it into words is just too straightforward...
くすぐったい 胸の奥がだから
...and tickles deep inside my chest, that's why!
がおってこ！がおってこ！ 「ありがとう」の代わりに
Roar away! Roar away! Instead of saying "thank you"...
がおってこ！がおってこ！ ここがそう 私たちの最高
...roar away! Roar away! This is indeed our absolute best!
ねえドクター ヘイドクター メンテしてよドクター
Hey Doctor, hey Doctor, give me some maintenance, Doctor!
またいつもの例のバグ
It's that usual bug of mine again.
ハッピー？ アンラッキー？ 一喜一憂するモード
Happy? Unlucky? I'm in a roller-coaster-of-emotions mode.
組み立てて 私式の鼓動 どこだ
Assemble it, where is my own style of heartbeat?
チチチチチチッ
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
チチチチチッた
Tick-tock, tick-tocked!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
おかしーね おかしーね くだらないね イェイイェイ
Isn't it strange? Isn't it strange? How silly, yay yay!
わけないね わけないね ハイスペックなんで
No big deal, no big deal, since I'm high-spec!
最先端のポン やらなきゃ損
A state-of-the-art clumsy girl, it's a loss if I don't do it!
ドキドキが止まりそう ねじ巻いて
My heartbeat is about to stop, so wind up my spring!
リルビ
Lilbi!
なんていうかエブリデイ ねじ巻いて ねじ巻いてよ
Like, everyday, wind my spring, please wind my spring!
ちょっとだけね ちょっちょっちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, ju-ju-just a little bit!
ピポパポ 鳴らしてよ
Make those beeping sounds for me!
夢を創る ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Creating a dream, just a little bit, just a little bit.
でもちょっとだけじゃ そのうち 足りなくなるかも
But before long, just a little bit might not be enough.
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ もう
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, geez!
チチチチチチッ
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
チチチチチッた
Tick-tock, tick-tocked!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
ねえドクター ドクター メンテしたのドクター
Hey Doctor, Doctor, did you do the maintenance, Doctor?
わけわからん わけわからん わけわからん らららららら
I don't get it, I don't get it, I don't get it, la la la la la la!
バグの呪いなんて祓おう
Let's ward off this bug's curse!
なんだかおっかないね おっかないね とんでもないね イェイイェイ
Somehow it's scary, it's scary, it's outrageous, yay yay!
これはもうテクノだ テクノロジーだ
This is already techno, it's technology!
三元素だって 持ってるもん
I even have the three primary elements!
分かったらその手ですぐ巻いて
If you understand, wind it up right now with that hand!
リルビ
Lilbi!
なんだっていいの笑って ねじ巻いて ねじ巻いてよ
Anything is fine, just laugh and wind my spring, wind it up!
ちょっとだけね ちょっちょっちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, ju-ju-just a little bit!
キミがミスっても 笑わせてあげる
Even if you make a mistake, I'll make you laugh.
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit.
ほら カラカラ カラカラ カラカラ アイデンティティ アップデートして
Look, clatter-clatter-clatter, update your identity!
どうもありがとう そこそこから リルビ リルビ
Thank you very much, from around there, Lilbi, Lilbi...
ピーポーパーポー ピーポーパーポー ピーコラー クリーヤー シャーンセー
Pipo papo pipo papo, picola cleeya shanse!
おきておきて 電気羊 ポッツラーニキーヤシャンセ
Wake up, wake up, electric sheep, pottsura nikiiya shanse!
その前にとりあえず ねじ巻いて
Before that, for now, wind my spring!
リルビ
Lilbi!
なんていうかエブリデイ ねじ巻いて ねじ巻いてよ
Like, everyday, wind my spring, please wind my spring!
ちょっとだけね ちょっちょっちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, ju-ju-just a little bit!
オーダーメイド 夢を創る
Custom-made, creating a dream,
ちょっとだけね ほんのちょっとだけね
just a little bit, just a tiny bit!
SFでも何でもいいけど 明日もちょっとだけ巻いて
Sci-fi or whatever is fine, but wind it a little tomorrow too.
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit.
こんな毎日も 悪くないよ
This kind of everyday life isn't so bad either,
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
just a little bit, just a little bit.
でもちょっとだけじゃ そのうち 足りなくなるかも
But before long, just a little bit might not be enough.
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
チチチチチチッ
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
チチチチチッた
Tick-tock, tick-tocked!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
チチチチチチッ
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
チチチチチッた
Tick-tock, tick-tocked!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi, Lilbi...
もう
Geez!
溺れたいな 会いたさぎゅっと
I want to drown, tightly holding my longing to meet you.
ハマる君の交差点
Falling deep into your intersection.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
I want to change, my feelings even more.
消えぬレイヤー 浮ついたままで
An unerasable layer, remaining flighty.
ネオンの眩しい夜が
The night with dazzling neon lights
行くあてもなく 過ぎ去って
passes by with nowhere to go.
薄暗いドアの向こう側
Beyond the dim door,
これって干渉した？
did we interfere with each other?
君の体温を 探しては
Searching for your body warmth,
アルコールで 振り付けた
choreographed with alcohol.
フロア このデシベルが 調和するように
So that this floor and these decibels will harmonize.
「気にしないで」なんて 言わないで
Please don't say "don't worry about it".
本当はいつも 正直じゃないけど
To be honest, I'm never quite truthful, but...
「気が付いてよ」なんて 言えなくて
I just can't bring myself to say "notice me".
嘘ばかり
Full of lies.
Just love you
溺れたいな
I want to drown,
会いたさぎゅっと ハマる君의交差点
tightly holding my longing to meet you, falling deep into your intersection.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
I want to change, my feelings even more.
ブルーを飲み干す体
Drinking down the blue body.
認めたくないな
I don't want to admit it,
I want to good
かなりギリの交差点
quite on the edge at the intersection.
変わりたいな
I want to change,
気持ちもっと
my feelings, even more,
言える？ ちょい危ないね
can I say it? It's a bit dangerous.
点滅と幻滅の間が
Between flashing lights and disillusionment is
永遠と快楽の狭間 1分待てないよ 好き嫌い
the threshold of eternity and pleasure, I can't wait a minute, love or hate.
ホワイトブラックすべて塗りつぶし Mommy
White and black, paint over it all,
強膜真っ赤に染めてどうした
sclera dyed bright red, what's wrong?
そんなに急がせないでよ ほらほら
Don't rush me so much, look, look,
ぐるぐるめくっちゃってく
spinning around, turning pages,
行ったり来たりどうだい？
going back and forth, how is it?
のらりくらりもいいじゃないけど
Aimless wandering is fine, but...
消えないシミと言い訳吐いて
Spitting out excuses and indelible stains,
耳の奥底で
deep inside my ears...
繰り返す イヤホンで聴き飽きた曲が
Looping... the song I'm tired of hearing on my earphones,
そのリピートと 交代するように
as if replacing that repeat.
気にしないでなんて言わないで
Don't tell me not to worry about it.
本当はいつも正直じゃないけど
Though I'm not really always honest,
気が付いてよなんて言えなくて保存しようか
but I can't bring myself to say, "Notice me."
そればかり
That's all it is...
溺れたいな
I want to drown,
I got you ぎゅっと
I got you tight,
はまる君の交差点
falling into your intersection.
変わりたいな
I want to change,
気持ちもっと
my feelings, even more,
ブルー飲み干す身体
my body drinking up the blue.
認めたくないな
I don't want to admit it,
I want to good
かなりギリの交差点
quite on the edge at the intersection.
変わりたいな
I want to change,
気持ちもっと
my feelings, even more,
言える？ ちょい危ないねよっしゃ
can I say it? It's a bit dangerous.
始まり！
Start!
もっとはまり！
Get hooked more!
愛して！
Love me!
骸ビーツ 死後のビーツ 骸ビーツ 死後のビーツ
Corpse beats, afterlife beats, corpse beats, afterlife beats.
骸ビーツ 死後のビーツ 裂けのビーツ 骸でビーツ
Corpse beats, afterlife beats, splitting beats, corpse beats.
死んじゃったらご愁傷 あの世でビーツ
Condolences if you die, beats in the afterlife,
でも存外楽しい 地獄でピース ピース ピース
but it's unexpectedly fun, peace, peace, peace in hell!
もうくよくよしないで
Don't worry anymore,
ほら 高い高いあやしてあげる
look, I'll lift you high and comfort you.
切り替えていこう
Let's switch gears!
ダンス ダンス チュチュ 骸とダンシング ダンシング チュチュチュ
Dance, dance, chu-chu, dancing with corpses, dancing chu-chu-chu,
キスでチュッチュッ
kiss with a chu-chu,
でもベッドはチュチュチュ
but in bed, chu-chu-chu.
ダンス ダンス チュチュ 腐乱とダンシング ダンシング チュチュチュ
Dance, dance, chu-chu, dancing with decay, dancing chu-chu-chu,
ビートに夢中チュ
obsessed with the beat,
甘酸っぱいチュチュチュ
sweet and sour chu-chu-chu.
ルワ ハリダドワ
Ruwa harida-dowa...
チュセダバダユソロ
Chusedabadayusoro!
踊ろう踊ろう死 君たちと踊ろう踊ろう
Let's dance, let's dance, death! Let's dance, let's dance with you all,
無限ハッピーハッピーエブリバディ それでいいじゃない
infinite happy, happy, everybody! Isn't that just fine?
愛したい誰からも愛されたいのって
I want to love, and I want to be loved by everyone.
よくないの？
Is that bad?
いけないの？
Is that not allowed?
あり余る不死をどうか許してね
Please forgive this overflowing immortality,
契約！わかったら返事！
it's a contract! Answer if you understand!
感動しました！泣けました！地獄最高！
I was moved! I cried! Hell is the best!
骸ビーツ 死後のビーツ 骸ビーツ 死後のビーツ
Corpse beats, afterlife beats, corpse beats, afterlife beats.
あっちとそっちで寂しいですか？
Is it lonely over there and over here?
ラミィがいるでしょう？
You have Lamy, right?
骸ビーツ 死後のビーツ
Corpse beats, afterlife beats.
誰がククロビン？ 愛 愛 愛
Who is Cock Robin? Love, love, love!
待って、どうせこの世なんて
Wait, this world is hopeless anyway.
待って、皆徒野の一つ
Wait, everyone is just a grave in the fields.
ねえ待って、通り過ぎてくだけなの？
Hey, wait, are you just passing by?
ねえ待ってって言ってんでしょ！
I said wait, didn't I!
いたってノリノリ
Extremely hyped up!
キュートが昂じてヘラった魔理の 根拠なく無敵な滾らせボディを
The depressed magic logic's groundlessly invincible, boiling body is...
こっそり蘇生中 なんて正義なチュチュチュ
secretly reviving! What a righteous chu-chu-chu!
悪夢みたいに窓を叩くから帰らないでおくれ
Since it knocks on the window like a nightmare, please don't go home!
断然ホットな夢中チュ
Decidedly hot and obsessed,
ハートビートはイエローチュ
heartbeat is yellow-chu,
調和 かなり調和 チュ
harmony, quite in harmony, chu!
喋ればヨソロ ビューティフル ビューティフル デス
If we talk, it's steady as she goes, beautiful beautiful death!
美しく笑おう笑おう
Let's laugh, let's laugh beautifully,
永遠にハグしてギュッとして ここってパラダイス
hug me forever, hold me tight, this is paradise!
みんなスキスキ何もかも手に入れたいんです
Love, love everyone, I want to get my hands on absolutely everything.
サチュナチュラル ぽきゅんボム
Saturational pokyun bomb!
ごめん 美人は死んでも治りません
Sorry, beautiful people don't recover even if they die!
ケラケラケラ ゲラ 脳解脱
Laughing, cackling, brain liberation...
laughing, cackling, brain liberation.
地獄謳歌
Enjoying hell to the fullest!
ケラケラケラ ゲラ 脳解脱
Laughing, cackling, brain liberation...
laughing, cackling, brain liberation.
ケラケラケラ
Cackling, cackling, cackling...
らったたりほー 月と踊れや踊れ
Rattatariho! Let's dance with the moon, dance!
らったた 頬を伝って歌えば風が吹く
Rattata! If you sing along your cheeks, the wind will blow.
らったたりほー みんなまだまだ上がるんだった
Rattatariho! Everyone, we're still going higher!
大波小波をかき分けて 出航！
Push through the big and small waves! Set sail!
アイ アイ マム！ 目元もっと ちゅ ちゅ ちゅ
Aye, aye, ma'am! Give those eyes more kisses!
遊び散らかして らったたりほー
Go wild and play, rattatariho!
アイ アイ マム！
Aye, aye, ma'am!
騒げばそこがアンダーワールドなんだよ 良い旅を
If you make a scene, that's the Underworld! Have a nice trip!
ラララ ララ ラララララララ
La la la, la la, la la la la la la la
ララララララララララララララ
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la
ラララ ララ ラララララララ
La la la, la la, la la la la la la la
ララララララララララララララ
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la
おどりゃしたならば 骸に花束を
Once we have danced, offer a bouquet to the corpse.
踊ろう 踊ろう 君たちと踊ろう 踊ろう
Let's dance, let's dance! Let's dance with all of you, let's dance!
愉快に ハッピーハッピーエブリバディ それでもいいんじゃない？
Cheerfully, happy happy everybody! Isn't that just fine?
すき すき すき すき 超愛してる
I love, love, love, love, love you so much!
それって良くないの？いけないの？
Is that bad? Is it not allowed?
ありあまるピストルを 許して 許して
Forgive my excess of pistols, forgive me, forgive me!
たったたと 髑髏になっても
Even if we rattle down to skeletons...
おーわらないカーニバル
It's a never-ending carnival!
楽しすぎて成仏しちゃいそう
It's so fun, I feel like ascending to heaven!
昇天しちゃう！
I'm passing on!
ののあらり ののあらり
Nonoarari, nonoarari...
君たち！船長のことを呼びとめて！
Everyone! Call out to the Captain!
契約成立
Contract established!
わかったら返事は？ね？
What's your answer if you understand? Right?
はーい！というわけで！
Okay! And with that!
7曲連続でお送りしました！
We performed seven songs in a row!
軽くここまでをね、振り返ってみましょう！
Let's quickly look back on them!
はーい！
Yay!
7曲ですよ、7曲。
Seven songs, seven whole songs.
サスペクト！ししろぼたん！
"Suspect"! Shishiro Botan!
ポルカとししろ、歌ったね。
Polka and Shishiro, you sang it.
良かった、歌えて。ダンスもかっこよかったよ！
I'm glad we did. The dancing was cool, too!
そしてねねの、魔法少女マジカルごじゃる、じゃきーん！
And then Nene's magical girl song, "Magical Gozaru", Ta-da!
良かったわ、あれも。
That was great too.
はい、ポルカ、ビビデバをやりました！
Yes, I, Polka, performed "Bibbidi-Babbidi-Boo"!
そしてメドレー。
And then the medley.
我らのね、オリ曲メドレー。
Yes, a medley of our original songs.
忙しかったけど楽しかった！最後バリバリなのマズいよね。
It was busy but fun! The last part being super intense was crazy.
最後はバリバリじゃないよ。
It wasn't "baribari" at the end.
最後は「ガオ」ってことだよ。
It was "Gao"!
「ガオ」って言っただろ、お前！
I told you it was "Gao"!
記憶がなくなってる！
My memory is completely gone!
間違えちゃった。
I made a mistake.
そのあとが、リリビですね。
And after that was "LiliVi"!
リリビ良かったよ！すごかった。
"LiliVi" was great! Awesome.
そのあと「インターセクション」、あづきちの曲ですね。一番好き。
Then "Intersection", Azuki's song. It's my absolute favorite.
最高や。
It's the best.
そして最後が。
And finally...
「すきすき大すき超愛してる」
"Suki Suki Daisuki Chou Aishiteru".
ちょっと難しかったね。でも本当に良かった。
It was a bit difficult, but really great.
船長って歌が上手なんだなって、すごい思いました。
I really felt once again that the Captain is a great singer.
改めて、先輩たちへの尊敬が生まれました。
It made me respect our seniors even more.
リスペクト！歌わせていただいて、ありがとうございました。
Respect! Thank you so much for letting us sing it.
ということで、ここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
With that, we have some happy news to share!
なになに？こちらをご覧ください！
What is it? Take a look at this!
どん！ねぽらぼアニバーサリーグッズ発売告知となります！
Ta-da! An announcement for the release of Nepolabo Anniversary goods!
こちらイラストはですね、にもし先生に描いていただきました！
These illustrations were drawn by Nimoshi-sensei!
今回は「天体パレード」という大テーマがあり、私たち「ねぽらぼ」は「占星術師」をテーマに描いていただきました。
This time, the main theme is "Celestial Parade," and we, Nepolabo, were illustrated under the theme of "Astrologers."
かわいい！ちょっとセクシーじゃない？
Cute! Isn't it a bit sexy?
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう。まずは、こちら！
Now let's look at the details. First up, this!
どん！プレミアムアクリル色紙です！
Ta-da! The Premium Acrylic Signboard!
イラストが綺麗に見えて、複製サインが入っているんです！
You can see the illustration beautifully, and it has replicated signatures!
綺麗だよ！
It looks beautiful!
続いては、こちら！アクリルスタンド！
Next up, this! Acrylic Stands!
豪華なアクリルスタンドとなっておりまして、大きさは15センチ程度を予定しております。
These are gorgeous acrylic stands, and the size is expected to be around 15 cm.
色紙とは異なる表情になっているので、色んなところで楽しめます。
They have different expressions compared to the signboard, so you can enjoy them anywhere.
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
はい、缶バッジセットでございます！
Yes, the Can Badge Set!
こちらも私たちの表情が楽しめる缶バッジセットとなっております。
This is also a badge set where you can enjoy our expressions.
そして続いては、こちら！
And next, this!
鍵モチーフキーホルダー！
Key-Motif Keychains!
私たちがビジュアルで持っている杖をイメージした鍵モチーフです。
They are designed keychains based on the staves we hold in the visual.
キーホルダーとなっております。
...is a key holder.
こちらは、一応、色が異なる、右上に小さなビジューがついてます。
These actually have different colors and a small jewel on the top right.
可愛い！ / おしゃれ！ / 欲しい！
So cute! / Stylish! / I want one!
そして続いては、こちら！
And next up is this!
コレクションボックスでございます！ / 何これ？
The Collection Box! / What's this?
本型ボックスに4人の鍵モチーフキーホルダーがセットになった...
A book-shaped box that comes with a set of our four key-motif keychains...
そんな感じになっております。
That's what it looks like.
表紙はもちろん、セレスティアル、裏表紙のデザインもこだわった、満足感たっぷりのボックスでございます！
The cover is Celestial, of course, and we paid close attention to the back cover too. It's a highly satisfying box!
いいね！買ってね！
Nice! Make sure to buy it!
さて、そしてさらにですね、お知らせがあります。
Now, we have even more announcements.
何、何？
What is it?
なんと、こちらです！
It's actually this!
お、何これ？
Oh, what is this?
ねぽらぼの新曲！
NePoLaBo's new song!
「めろどーま」が、このあと18日の0時からデジタルリリース！
"Melodoma" will be digitally released at midnight tonight on the 18th!
やったー！
Yay!
「めろどーま」って一体なんなんだ？
What on earth is Melodoma?
このあと新曲をお披露目しますので、絶対に聴いてください！
We'll perform the new song after this, so please make sure to listen!
よろしくお願いします！ / めろどーま！
Please look forward to it! / Melodoma!
そしてですね、我ら5期生3周年ということで、各自のチャンネルにて...
And since it's our 5th generation 3rd anniversary, on our respective channels...
MVがアップされておりますので、ぜひチェックしてみてください！
MVs have been uploaded, so please check them out!
ラミィが「コズミック・ワンダフル・ツアー」を上げております。
Lamy uploaded "Cosmic Wonderful Tour."
ねねは「ハイパージャンピン」！
Nene uploaded "Hyper Jumpin'"!
ぼたんは「ひとつになるコエ」を上げてます。
Botan uploaded "Hitotsu ni Naru Koe".
ポルカは「トウィンクルフォーユー」を上げてます。
Polka uploaded "Twinkle 4 You".
見てください！
Please watch them!
じゃあ、個人のお知らせいこうか！
Now, let's move on to individual announcements!
そうですね。ラミィが8月15日に発売した...
Right. Lamy's first album, released on August 15th...
ファーストアルバム「Fleur de neige」が予約受付中となっております！
"Fleur de neige," is now available for pre-order!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
ねねは、オリ曲の「ごきげんドリンクバー」のMVが出ております！
Nene has released the MV for her original song, "Gokigen Drink Bar"!
あと、ソロライブの配信チケット、まだ販売中なのでチェックよろしくお願いします！
Also, streaming tickets for my solo live are still on sale, so please check them out!
ポルカです！ポルカの「燦然燃焼」のフルアニメーションMVが出ました！みんな、いっぱい観てね！
It's Polka! The full-animation MV for my "Sanzen Nenshou" is out! Everyone, watch it a lot!
私はですね、個人3周年グッズ発売中でございます。ぜひ手に入れてみてください。
As for me, my individual 3rd anniversary goods are now on sale. Please check them out!
そして、私誕生日が9月なので...
And since my birthday is in September...
そろそろ誕生日のお知らせも後々発表できると思いますので...
I should be able to announce my birthday celebration soon...
ぜひ、Xなり私のチャンネルなりチェックしてみてください！
So please check my X account or channel!
はーい！
Okay!
というわけで、以上、ねぽらぼアニバーサリーグッズ情報とリリース情報でした！
And that's all for NePoLaBo's anniversary merchandise and release info!
はい、というわけで、いよいよライブもクライマックス！
Alright, the live show is finally reaching its climax!
ラストはさっきの新曲を踊って歌って、やりたいと思います！
For our last song, we're going to sing and dance to our new song!
やったー！
Yay!
みんな、めろどーまになる準備はいい？
Are you all ready to become Melodoma?
みんなコメントの準備もちょっとしてほしいな、めろどーま。よろしくお願いします。
Prepare your comments for Melodoma too! Thank you!
そして、ラストは魔導ゴンドラに乗って歌いたいと思います！
And finally, we will sing while riding the magic gondola!
魔導ゴンドラってなんだ？
What's a magic gondola?
みんな、準備はいいですか？
Is everyone ready?
みんな、めろどーまの準備して！
Everyone, get ready for Melodoma!
じゃあ、これはめろどーまもこれ極大魔法か？
So, is Melodoma also a grand magic spell?
でかそうだよね。
It sounds pretty grand.
上からゴンドラが降りてくるので、みんなで一緒に「めろどーま」って言って、こっちは喋るでいいか？
The gondola will descend, so let's all say "Melodoma" together, and then I'll talk, okay?
オッケー！
Okay!
せーの、めろどーま！
One, two... Melodoma!
おー！来た！
Oh! It's here!
来る？来た来た！
Is it coming? It's here, it's here!
おー！
Oh!
来ました！
It has arrived!
これ乗れる？
Can we get on this?
乗れますかね、乗りましょう。
I think we can. Let's get on.
はーい、乗ってください。
Alright, please hop on.
じゃあね、皆さん、最後は盛り上がっていきましょう！
Alright everyone, let's turn up the hype for the grand finale!
曲名もう一回言っちゃう？
Should we say the song title one more time?
じゃあ、みんな聴いてください。せーの、めろどーま！
Then everyone, please listen to... One, two, Melodoma!
とろけちゃってラビュ
Melting for you, love you...
ずっと ずっと
...forever and ever,
頭の中ハート
my head is full of hearts.
いっぱいになって
Overflowing,
ほら もっともっと
look, more and more,
釘付けになれ めろどーま
be absolutely transfixed! Melodoma!
Ever Lasting Love Me...
女の子は魔法使い
Girls are magic-users,
神様がくれたプレゼント
a present given by God.
恋しちゃったりだって
Even falling in love...
思わせぶりだって
...or being a tease...
必然的アウトかな
...is it naturally out?
甘い酸っぱいほろ苦い
Sweet, sour, bittersweet...
カラフルなポーション 使い分けて
...using colorful potions for different times.
君にかけたい呪文 ささやくの
Whispering the spell I want to cast on you...
なんて...
...How...
なんて恥ずかしい妄想が
...embarrassing. My delusions...
胸の中を駆け巡る ギルティ
...run wild in my heart. Guilty!
だって そばにいてほしいから
Because I want you by my side.
広がる呪文
The spreading spell...
めろぞーま
Melozoma!
とろけちゃって ラビュー ずっとずっと
I'm melting, love you forever and ever,
頭の中ハートいっぱいになって
my head is filling up with hearts.
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more,
釘付けになれ めろぞーま
keep your eyes glued on us, Melozoma!
レディーファーストってなんか嫌
I don't really like "ladies first,"
私ファーストが絶対です
for me, "me first" is an absolute must!
優しさも温もりも
Kindness, warmth,
時間も感情だって
even your time and emotions...
独占させて fall in love
let me monopolize them all, fall in love!
カラフルだけどトゲがあって
Colorful but with thorns,
こんぺいとうみたいなこの純情
this pure heart is just like star candy.
食べて欲しいな
I want you to eat it.
ほら あーん口開けて
Come on, say "ah" and open your mouth.
まただ おかしな思考回路が
Once again, my strange thought process...
自律神経バグらす メルティ
is messing with my nervous system, Melty.
こんな気持ち初めてなんだ
This is the first time I've felt this way.
わけもわからずに めろぞーま
Without even knowing why, Melozoma!
とろけちゃって ラビュー ずっとずっと
I'm melting, love you forever and ever,
両目見つめハートいっぱいになって
staring into your eyes, my heart fills up.
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more,
溺れてしまえ めろぞーま
drown in it completely, Melozoma!
この魔法がずっと解けないように
So that this magic will never wear off...
呪いと等しい類かもしれないけど
It might be something close to a curse, but...
君といつまでもとろけていたいから
I want to melt with you forever.
ありったけの魔力を込めて
Pouring in all the magic power I have...
君と出会った瞬間から始まった
Since the very moment I met you,
このロマンスが
this romance has begun...
ソーダみたいにはじける
...bursting like soda.
なんて辛いよ
It's so painful!
永遠になんて空想
"Forever" is just a fantasy...
だけど願いたいの
...but I still want to wish for it.
そんな魔法があればいいのに
If only such magic existed...
切ないけど
It's heartbreaking, but...
素直になりたい めろぞーま
I want to be honest, Melozoma!
唱えたいな ラビュー ずっとずっと
I want to chant "love you" forever and ever,
こんなにも君に恋してるから
because I'm so deeply in love with you.
離れたくない ハグ もっともっと
I don't want to leave, hug me more and more,
想い愛したい めろぞーま
I want us to love each other, Melozoma!
とろけちゃって ラビュー ずっとずっと
I'm melting, love you forever and ever,
頭の中ハート充満になって
my head is completely filled with hearts.
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more,
釘付けになれ めろぞーま
Keep your eyes glued on us, Melozoma!
解けないで とっておきの魔法
Don't wear off, my very special magic.
クラクラさせてやる メルティ
I'll make you feel dizzy, Melty!
いつまでも私だけ見てて
Keep looking only at me forever,
唱える めろぞーま
as I chant Melozoma!
解けないで とっておきの呪文
Don't wear off, my very special spell.
ドキドキしたいの メルシー
I want my heart to race, Merci!
いつまでも私を愛してね
Please love me forever and ever,
唱える めろぞーま
as I chant Melozoma!
イチコロね めろぞーま
You're a goner now, Melozoma!